# Benjamin Villa Williston VT 05495 802-505-1138

## benjamin.j.villa@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/benjaminjvilla/

## **Objective:**

I'm a results-oriented team player focused on communication and productivity. I work best with clearly defined goals and pride myself on my resourcefulness and creativity to reach those goals. Over the past years, I've honed existing skills and actively worked at improvement in areas outside of my comfort zone. I've proven dedication and drive through many diverse roles within a company, continually taking on more responsibility.

I welcome any challenges that require unique perspective and creative problem solving and I look forward to an exciting new position that will allow full use of my existing skills but will also continue to provide opportunities for new growth and learning.

#### **Education:**

- Bachelor of Arts, Castleton University, Castleton, VT
  - Studied Theatre Arts, Music, and Logic
- Burlington Code Academy, Upright Education, Burlington, VT

0

## <u>Technical Skills & Competencies:</u>

Technical Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React

Competencies:

## **Professional Experience:**

Lead Asset Protection Coordinator, Hannaford Supermarkets, VT, Oct. 2020 - Jan. 2022

•

Asset Protection Coordinator, Hannaford Supermarkets, VT, Mar. 2017 - Oct. 2020

•

Retail Associate(Various Positions), Hannaford Supermarkets, VT, Apr. 2008 - Mar. 2017

•

## **Awards & Achievements:**

• Alpha Psi Omega - Inductee, 2012